翻译: 莫言
校对: 柿子
你从哪冒出来的哟 小肉肉
Where did you come from, flubber?
校对: 柿子
"哈啰 Hal"
"Hello, Hal."
校对: 柿子
"哈啰 Hal"
"Hello, Hal."
校对: 柿子
后期: 店小二
"哈啰 Hal"
"Hello, Hal."
后期: 店小二
*培根在我肚 肥肉在我腹*
I'm so full of bacon, my body's meant for shakin'
后期: 店小二
压制: 凯撒
*培根在我肚 肥肉在我腹*
I'm so full of bacon, my body's meant for shakin'
压制: 凯撒
*我随心而动 我胸也微摇*
And when I start to wiggle, my nipples, they will jiggle
- 你还是真是丢人丢到你外婆家了  - 对
Once again I have to be embarrassed for the both of us. Yep!
电波诚译
马尔柯姆的一家
第三季 第九集
你放学后直接去上班
You go straight for your job after school today.
可别第一天上班就迟到 也别给我找借口
I don't want you to be late for your first day of work. And no excuses!
我可不想听说什么"有狮子从动物园跑出来了"
I don't wanna hear, "A lion escaped from the zoo",
或者"校车司机疯了不肯停车之类的鬼话"
or, "The bus driver went insane and refused to stop."
Francis的朋友给Reese在马戏团汉堡店找了份工作
Francis's friend gave Reese a job at the Circus Burger.
太合我意了
It's perfect.
Reese整天都得被呼来唤去
Reese gets to be bossed around all day
还是被全世界唯一一个比他还蠢的人使唤
by the only guy on the planet that's dumber than he is.
- 这个工作太蠢了  - 但是你可以戴个纸帽子啊
- This job is stupid! - You do get to wear a paper hat.
Reese 你要想拿到驾照就开车
Reese, you wanna drive when you get your license,
你得自己付保险
you have to pay your own insurance!
别人都投保了 我干嘛要去投呢
Yeah, but everyone else has insurance! Why do I need it?
出事了别人的保险会赔偿的
They've got it covered.
儿啊 事情并没有这么简单啊 比如说
Son, it's not as simple as that. You see...
早上好 各位 Charlie 给大家问好
Good morning, everybody! Say good morning, Charlie.
让大家看看你多有活力
Show everyone how alive you are.
我爸妈跟Dewey做了个交易
My parents made a deal with Dewey.
两个月之内他保金鱼不死 他就可以养条狗了
If he keeps his goldfish alive for two months, he gets a dog.
- 我做得是不是很好啊  - 当然是
- Am I doing a good job? - You sure are.
- 这鱼怎么还活着呢  - 我也不知道啊
- How is that fish still alive? - I don't know
他从不喂鱼 还把它扔在外面晒太阳
He never feeds it and he leaves it out in the sun for hours.
上周鱼缸里还有香蕉皮呢
Last week there was an old banana peel in there!
我可不要养条狗
I do not want a dog in this house!
只要这条鱼还活着 我们就没办法
As long as the fish is alive, there is nothing we can do about it.
Hal 我可指望着你处理这事儿
Hal, I expect you to take care of this.
- 你在暗示什么  - 我什么都没说
- What are you suggesting? - I'm not suggesting anything.
我只想你好好"照顾"它一下
I just want it taken care of.
各位同学 今天我们开始新一轮的自主学习计划
Class, today we begin a new round of independent study projects.
流体静力平衡学
Hydrostatic equilibrium?
天哪 我还在学路径积分分量化方程
My God, I am still my Path integral quantisation
我后爸说的对 我就是个废物
My stepdad's right,I'm useless.
生活中一个残酷而冰冷的事实是
Well, the cold, hard fact of life
有些人生来就比别人聪明
is some are more advanced than others.
甚至还有些人认为自己比我还聪明
Some even think they're more advanced than me.
我从来没这么说过
I never said that.
那你干嘛以为我在说你
Yet you assume I'm talking about you.
你正对着我说的啊
You're looking right at me!
我相信你们都认为自己是天才少年班的学生
I'm sure you're all convinced by virtue of you being in this class,
所以你们的智商远高于
your intellects tower above those of
这个学校其他只会浪费氧气的普罗大众
tiny plebeians wasting oxygen in the rest of the school.
但是 对某些人而言 你不过是
But, to some, you are nothing more
只会瞎吵胡闹的猩猩
than howling primates.
我今天很高兴地告诉大家
I'm excited to announce today
我们班上将迎来一位新同学
that we're welcoming to our class a new student.
一个智冠群雄的年轻人
A young man of unparalleled intellect.
据我们推测 他的智商超过了280
As near as we can measure, his IQ is over 280.
这些智商测试有文化偏见
Those tests are culturally biased!
随便你怎么想
Think what you will.
我已经不再在意你们狭隘的恐惧感了
Your petty fears no longer concern me.
我终于找到了值得我雕琢的美玉
I finally have the mental clay worthy of my sculpting.
Barton是一颗炽热的智慧星
Barton is a white-hot comet of brilliance,
划过我们无知的黑暗角落
blazing through our dark little corner of ignorance.
具备深不可测的智慧
A mind of such unfathomable reach
- 和无与伦比的力量  - 我可以进来了吗
- and enormous power. - Can I come in now?
Barton 我不是告诉你等到我说
Barton, I thought I told you to wait till you heard,
"人类新纪元"之后再进来吗
"A new era for man."
但是外面有只蜜蜂
But there's a bee out there.
不错哦 助理主管 怎么当上的啊
So, assistant manager. How's that happen?
移民局突击检查 Quendus被驱逐出境
INS raid, Quendus out.
每周一三四 十二点到五点
So, from 12 to 5, Monday, Wednesday, Thursday,
这就是我的底盘了
this is my domain.
我证明了 事业成功不用高中毕业
I'm proof you don't need to graduate high school.
那都是宣传
That's just propaganda
好让毕业文凭公司多赚钱
from those money-grabbing diploma companies.
Sean Doug 这是Reese
Sean, Doug, this is Reese.
- 嘿 你好  - 嘿
- Hey. what's up? - Hey.
好了 要汉堡就按奶牛键 薯条按土豆键
OK. Press cow for burger, potato for fries.
我也不知道这个是干吗的
And I'm not sure what this is.
你看像猪还是像狗
Does that look like a pig or a dog to you?
在按键上写上单词不是更易懂点吗
Wouldn't it be easier to put words on the keys?
哈 有才啊
Ah, a man of letters.
聪明人一点就通
A word to the wise.
一般人我可不这么表扬啊
I wouldn't throw that in anyone's face.
收到钱后放到这个抽屉里
Once you get your total, you put the money in the drawer,
- 除非你想揩零  - 什么是揩零
except you are making a pocket transactions. What's that?
鼓舞士气的方法
Kind of a morale builder.
你偶尔收到5块10块的零钱时
Once in a while take 5 or 10 bucks.
你不进收银机而是放进自己的口袋
but you don't ring it up, put it in your pocket instead.
你对这没意见吧
You don't have a problem with that, do you?
没 当然没
Oh, no. That's cool.
Reese 欢迎来到工作的世界
See, Reese. You've entered the working world.
一个肩负成人责任的世界
A world of adult responsibility.
我有她更衣箱的钥匙
I have the key to her locker.
你要是想闻闻她的外套啊什么的 跟我说
If you wanna smell her jacket later, just let me know.
嘿 听说他们找到那人尸体最后一块儿了
Hey, they found the last piece of that guy.
我靠
Oh, man!
各位 我们之前讨论过这个的
Come on, guys. We talked about this.
如果我们要共用卫生纸
If we're gonna share a roll of toilet paper,
麻烦大家把它放在卷筒上
can we at least keep it on the spindle?
既然你提到了这个事情
As long as you are bringing this kinda of stuff up,
我未婚妻周四过来
I got a fiancee coming Thursday.
- 未婚妻 什么未婚妻啊  - 我订过婚的
Fiancee? What are you taking about? I'm engaged.
时机一到 欢场浪子也回头
It comes to time when a man gets tired of playing the field.
什么浪子 你连个女人都不认识
What field? You don't even know any women.
我也知道
That occurred to me, too,
所以我从俄罗斯订了一个
That's why I ordered one from Russia.
邮寄新娘吗 还有这东西啊
A mail-order bride? That actually exists?
当然 在苏联某些不开化的地方
Sure. In some of the more irradiated parts of former Soviet Union,
有很多这种一心想要结婚的女人
there are a lot of marriage-minded women.
我亲爱的Svetlana就是其中一个
That's my darling Svetlana.
等等 嗯
Wait a second. Yep.
就是Svetlana
Svetlana.
今天怎么是你送我们去上学啊
How come you're driving us to school?
妈妈偶尔也会干这活的
Because that's what moms do sometimes.
啊
Argh!
好吧 你知道托尔斯泰和艾略特
OK, you know your Tolstoy and your Eliot...
让我们见识见识你对宫廷诗人的了解
Let's see how you do with the Bard.
"君子华服 汝贼适之"
"Every true man's apparel fits your thief."
第四场 第二幕
Measure For Measure, Act 4, Scene 2.
Elbow对Pompey说的一句话
Elbow says to Pompey.
麻烦你把绿色蜡笔递给我
Could you hand me my green crayon?
- 哇 他又对了  - 好的 Barton
- Wow, he's right again. -  OK, Barton
我们再来试试乔叟的
let's try Chaucer's The Shipman's Tale.
- 我可以从序言开始吗  - 拜托 第203行
- Should I start with the prologue? - Please. How about line 203?
"当你丈夫去往佛兰德斯时"
"And when your husband has gone off to Flanders,"
"我会将你从对诽谤的恐惧中解救出来"
"I shall deliver you from fear of slanders,"
"说着他抓住她的肩膀"
"and on the word he caught her by the flanks"
"紧紧把她拥入怀中 狂野地吻了过去"
"and clasped her closely, giving her a riot of kisses,"
"轻声言道 不要声张"
"saying softly, 'Keep things quiet'"
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
乔叟 你们居然毒害他的思想
Chaucer? I cannot believe you're polluting his mind
给他看这么低俗不堪的垃圾
with such pop culture drivel!
我替他们道歉 Barton
I apologise for them, Barton.
我会尽我所能减少他们这些烦人的干扰
I'll do everything I can to minimise these annoying distractions
以便让你的注意力集中在
so that you can concentrate on the accelerated programme
我为你制定的加速计划上
I've laid out for you.
我们势必共同震惊世界
Together we are gonna astonish the world.
吃不吃糖管啊
Would you like a pixy stix?
谢谢
Thank you.
有问题吗 Malcolm
Having problems, Malcolm?
不 不 你不会有问题的
No, no, not you
该死的流体静力平衡学 完全没意义
It's the stupid hydrostatic equilibrium. It doesn't make sense!
这是很难很难很难 但是别灰心
It is awfully difficult. But don't despair.
有我呢 Malcom
I'm here for you, Malcom.
我保证你会得到你应有的帮助的
I'll make sure you get the help you deserve.
为估算太阳中心的压强
To estimate the pressure at the centre of the sun,
只需假设其恒定密度为1.41克每立方厘米
just assume a constant density of 1.41 grams per cubic cm.
我是不是说太快了啊
Am I going too fast for you?
Herkabe是为了羞辱我才让你指导我的
You know, Herkabe only made you my tutor to humiliate me.
我还以为是为了羞辱我呢
I thought it was to humiliate me.
我就不懂了 这鬼东西怎么这么难
I don't understand why is this so hard?!
别放弃 还记得吗
Don't give up. Remember The Little Engine That Could?
你根本没明白
You're not listening!
我什么都知道
I get everything!
我这辈子就没有什么东西学不会的
In my entire life, there is nothing I haven't been able to master.
我六年级就学了代数学
I took algebra in 6th grade!
我五岁时就教会我爸怎么重组变速器
I taught my dad how to rebuilt his transmission when I was five!
我会走之前就识字了
I was reading before I could walk!
- 我记得我自己出生的过程  - 什么
I remember my own birth. What?!
你知道你妈子宫收缩的时候你的心跳会停止吗
D'you know your heart stops during your mother's contractions?
你真记得那些吗
You seriously remember that?
最糟糕的是换尿片
Worst was the diaper changing.
那是我这辈子活得最没尊严的一周
That was the most degrading week of my life.
那么 你那里面是什么情况
So, what's it like in there?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你大脑里
Well, your brain?
对我而言 当我思考太用力的时候
I mean, for me it's like, when I'm thinking really hard,
我大脑里开始各种联想
my brain starts making all these connections.
层出不穷的联想
Those connections make other connections,
感觉计算速度飞快
Everything starts to moving really fast.
接着大脑就像要爆炸了似的
Then it feels like a bomb's going off.
你也这样吗
Is yours like that?
我的大脑更像个蜂箱
It's more like a beehive.
里面每只蜜蜂都有个像你一样的大脑
And every bee has a brain like yours.
准备好了
OK, ready!
帅爆了
That is so cool!
要是有支枪就好了
I wish you had a gun
那我们就能真正测试这个玻璃的性能了
so we can really test this out.
不好意思 点单
Excuse me. Can I get some help here?
嗨 Greg
Hi, Greg.
我无意中听到你妈讲电话
So I overheard your mom talking on the phone
你还真在这上班啊
and it's true. You've got a job.
我申请过这里的工作 可惜没拿到
I applied here once. Didn't get it.
- 都怪政治  - 可能吧
- It's all politics. - I guess.
- 你要点什么  - 仔细听好
- So what do you want? - I want you to listen very carefully.
我现在血糖指标已经非常低了
My blood sugar's dangerously low
我不想再劳神费心给你说第二遍
so I don't wanna burn up calories repeating myself.
我要一个巨无霸汉堡配大份薯条
I want the jumbo clown burger with big top fries,
不要腌黄瓜 一片洋葱 只要中间部分
no pickles, a slice of onion, make sure it's centre cut,
还有多放西红柿
and extra tomatoes.
肉饼要一面全熟 一面五分熟
And let's do the pattie well on one side, medium on the other.
汉堡胚要新做的
Make sure they open a fresh package for my bun.
不新鲜的话 我就走人
If it's stale I bail.
说真的
Seriously.
总共5块4毛5 可乐还可免费续杯
Your total's $5.45 and you get free refills on the soda.
早就知道了 不过仅限今天
Heard that one before. Turns out it's just for today.
混球
What a sack!
这可是揩零的大好机会啊
That's a pocket transaction if I ever saw one.
哦 是的
Oh, yeah. Right.
Artie 你这个单身派对办得太完美了
Artie, you put together one hell of a bachelor party.
我很感谢你
I'm much obliged to you.
就是对不住大家 最近的脱衣舞女在300英里外
I'm just sorry the nearest stripper's 300 miles away.
嘿 她现在怎么样了啊
Hey, how's she doin' anyway?
她刚把上衣全脱了
She took her top off!
噢耶
Oh, yeah!
各位 听我说几句
Listen up! I'd like to say a few words about my mate Pete,
我的老朋友Pete就要结婚了
on account of his upcoming nuptials.
多少次我情绪低落时
Many's the time, when I've been feeling low,
我都知道我总还有Pete
and I always knew I could turn to Pete.
他就这样躺在他的床上 用打火机修胡子
He'd be lying on his bunk, trimming his beard with a lighter,
我就会想 "妈的 我总比他这样强"
and I'd think, "Hell, I'm better than that."
敬Pete和他幸运的新娘
To Pete and his lucky lady!
你怎么回事啊
What's going on with you?
我就是不知道我们都在庆祝什么
I just don't get what are we celebrating?
总感觉不对
I mean, it just seems wrong.
这是Pete的生活
It's Pete's life.
他要想娶一个陌生人 那是他的事
If he wants to marry a total stranger, that's his business.
那新娘怎么办 有谁想过她
What about this woman? Is anyone thinking about her?
我现在只想想着这个没穿上衣的脱衣舞女
Right now I'm trying to keep a topless stripper in my head.
实在没心思想别的了
I don't have room for much else.
想想看
Think about it for a second.
她就这样盲目地许下一个承诺
She's blindly committing
把余生荒废在这个鬼地方
to spend her life in this god forsaking place
还要做Pete的老婆
with Pete as her husband.
这得是有多可怜才能落到这种下场啊
What kind of poor creature would actually go through with this?
说不定她现在的生活也很糟糕呢
Maybe her life's pretty awful.
比这还糟吗
Worse than this?
她是活在集中营么
What? Does she live in a slaughterhouse?
她是每天要被马拖着去上班么
Is she dragged to work by horses every day?
她完全不知道她要面临的是什么样的生活
She couldn't possibly know what she's getting into.
别夸大其词了 我们也不知道
You're exaggerating. We don't know.
最终结果没准还不错呢
It might work out fine.
兄弟 生意怎么样啊
Dude, how's business?
你去哪了 我本该回家吃晚饭了
Where were you? I was supposed to be home for dinner
可没你我还下不了班
but you are the only one who can cash me out.
我要是你的话 还是乖一点
Hey, I'd stay on my good side if I was you.
就这几天 有人要打扫卫生间了哟
One of these days somebody'll have to clean these bathrooms.
哇 太不像话了
Whoa, this is way uncool.
Reese 你可不能一下拿这么多钱啊
Reese, you can't take this much money.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
收银机 瞧 少了400块
Your cash drawer, man.. It is over $400 bucks short. Look.
揩零的精髓就在于拿个5块10块就行了
The whole point is to take five or ten bucks. That's it.
你得把那400块放回来
You got to put the 400 back.
我没拿 真没拿
I didn't take it. Honest.
兄弟 这可是你的收银机
Dude. It's your register.
- 他今天把钥匙给别人了吗  - 没给
- Did he give his register key to anyone today? - No.
我没拿钱 我什么都没拿
I didn't take it. I didn't take any.
我连一次揩零都没揩
I never even do one of those stupid pocket transactions.
你说什么呢 我昨天还看你拿了呢
What do you talking about? I saw you yesterday.
没 我只是装装样子 其实我没拿
No, I wanted it to look like I was taking it. But I didn't really.
我趁你们没注意的时候把钱放回去了
When you guys weren't looking I put the money back.
你们都没看到 我是偷偷地放进去的
You guys didn't see it cos I was being... sneaky and stuff.
不错嘛 Reese
Nice, Reese.
- 谢谢你全家  - 我没拿
- Way to screw it up for everybody. - I didn't take it!
听着 这事如果你想着我会罩你 你就别指望了
Look, man. If you are thinking that I'm coverin' for you, you are crazy.
店老板明天早上来检查账目的时候
When the owner comes back tomorrow morning and checks the books,
这钱最好得在这 要不然你麻烦可就大了
that money better be herel, or you're going down.
星等是衡量天体光度的量
在全光谱范围内由视星等转换到绝对星等
Alright. The change from apparent to absolute magnitude in all spectra
转换方程为
The formula is...
A与B的比值乘以K与D的比值 如果K是
A over B times K over D. That's if K is...
这么多公式怎么记得住啊
How do they expect you to learn all these formulas?
用点记忆技巧
Use a mnemonic device,
比如说Enephru Babashar Kalar Dastrer
like Enephru, Babashar, Kalar, Dastrer.
都是巴比伦第三王朝的国王
Babylonian kings, Third Dynasty.
别埋怨了 我也有家庭作业要做
Stop complaining. I have homework, too.
啊 这是个蝴蝶
Ah, it's a butterfly.
Malcolm 快帮帮我
Malcolm, you got to help me.
- 怎么回事  - 事大了
- What's goin' on? - It's horrible.
今天我值班的时候 收银机里少了400块
There is $400 missing from my register during my shift,
他们以为是我拿了
and they think I took it.
- 那是你拿的吗  - 当然不是
- Well, did you? - No, of course not!
- 我是Barton  - 这个小矮子是谁啊
- I'm Barton. - Who's this dork?
- 他是我的家教  - 我靠
- He is my tutor. - You're kiddin' me!
我就这么一次需要你的天才智慧
The one time I need you to be a genius
结果发现你是个冒牌货
I find you've been faking the whole smart thing.
Reese 冷静点 事情怎么会这样呢
Reese, calm down. How did this happen?
我也不知道
I don't know.
交班的时候我收银机里的钱对不上账了
My register didn't total up right at the end of the shift.
- 当时都有谁在场  - 都在
- Who was there? - Everyone.
我 Sean Greta和Richie
Me, Sean, Greta, Richie.
Richie也在 你怎么不早说啊
Richie? Why didn't you say so at the first place?
他在怎么啦
What do you mean?
肯定是Richie搞鬼 是他陷害了你
It's Richie. He's setting you up.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为他是Richie 拜托
Because it's Richie! C'mon!
Barton 想不想见识一下真实世界
Barton, you wanna learn something about the real world?
- 不是很想  - 太可惜了
- Not really. - Too bad.
你得一起来
You're coming.
Dewey 给我们打个掩护
Dewey, you have to cover it for us.
让爸妈感觉我们一直都在
Make sure it sounds like we're all still here.
知道了
Got it.
嗷 住手
Ow! Stop it!
你住嘴
You shut up!
你个蠢蛋
Stupid creeps!
嗷 住手
Ow! Stop it!
- 弄到手了吗  - 弄到了
- Did you get it? - Yes, I got it.
宠物店老板跟我说这鱼已经死了
Pet store owner told me it was already dead,
但我感觉情况更糟
but I suspect the worst.
好的 我们今晚趁Dewey睡着了就把鱼掉包
OK. Let's switch the fish tonight when Dewey's sleeping.
我不知道 Lois 总感觉很卑鄙
I don't know, Lois. It seems so sneaky and underhanded.
我们这是要给孩子们树立怎样的榜样啊
What kind of example are we setting for the boys?
Hal 别担心
Well, Hal, stop worrying.
孩子们没事的
The boys are fine.
兄弟 弄到钱了吗
Hey dude, did you get the money?
哼 你还想再要400块 是吧
Yeah, you'd like another 400, wouldn't you?
你什么意思啊你
What are you talking about?
哇 一整套寄生系统群落呢
Wow! An entire colony of parasitica.
一边吃披萨去 Dewey
Get your own pizza, Dewey.
他不叫Dewey
His name's not Dewey.
那这些年你们让我叫他Dewey干嘛
How come you had me call him that all these years?
听着 我们知道你拿了那笔钱
Look. We know you took the money
还想栽赃给Reese
and you're trying to pin it on Reese.
你个白眼狼 我哥给你帮了多少忙啊
After everything my brother's done for you!
给你做不在场证明 帮你发传单
All the alibis, all the handouts,
- 还一直帮你装死  - 兄弟
- all the times he's helped you fake your death! - Whoa! Dudes!
我今天都没在店里
I wasn't even there today.
我就在交接的时候去了一趟
The only time I came in was to cash out.
你当时也在场
You were right there.
是这样 但是我四点半的时候休息了十分钟
Yeah, but I had a ten-minute break at 4:30.
你可以趁机溜进去偷钱
You could have snuck in then and take the money.
- 是的 但  - 你想装无辜
- Yeah, but... - You wanna play innocent?
好 我们让警察来决定
Fine. We'll just let the police decide.
叫警察啊
Whoa, police.!
你凭什么认为条子会站在你那边
What makes you think the cops are gonna take your side?
可能因为你已经犯了十多次盗窃罪
Maybe cos you've been arrested like 10 times for petty theft.
不好意思 有一次是因为纵火
Excuse me, one of those was for arson.
我跟你讲 你犯了个大错
I am telling you, you're making a big mistake.
- 才没有  - 就有
- No, I'm not! - Yes, you are!
- 就没有  - 你确实错了
- No, I'm not! - Yes, you are.
他没偷那笔钱 照这张传票来看
He didn't do it. According to this citation,
四点二十的时候Richie在威尔逊18号
Richie was stopped at 4:20 at 18th and Wilson
因行车小便被警察拦了下来
for urinating from a moving vehicle.
- 然后呢  - 马戏团汉堡店在沃纳特
- So? - So the Circus Burger is on Walnut,
两地相隔至少有25英里
which is at least 25 miles away.
他不可能在Reese休息的时候赶到的
He couldn't have got there during Reese's break.
如果路上不堵
Well what if the traffic was light..
而且一辆78年的博纳维尔可以开到300英里每小时
Yeah. And maybe if a '78 Bonneville could go 300 miles an hour.
否则的话不可能
Otherwise, it's impossible.
嘿 不错嘛 Dewey
Hey, way to go, Dewey!
- 让我看看这个  - 他是对的吗
- Let me see that. - Is he right?
是的 他永远是对的
Yes. He's always right.
不好意思 Richie 我们走吧 Reese
Sorry, Richie. Come on, Reese, let's go.
但是我发誓没有拿那钱啊 我没拿啊
But I swear to God, I didn't do it. I didn't take the money!
别急 我们还有几个小时
Well, look. We still have a few hours.
或许我们可以想个
Maybe we can figure...
Richie 我买到这个DVD播放器了
Richie, I got us this DVD player
但是我们还要 再去偷个600块
but we need to steal another 600
如果你想要环绕立体声
if you want the surround...
音响的话
..sound.
估计你得留好收据
You may wanna hang on to that receipt.
你居然对我们说谎了
I can't believe you lied!
我要报警
We are calling the cops!
嘿 嘿 嘿 或许我们可以私了
Hey-ey-ey. Maybe we could figure out some sort of a deal?
随便你们提什么条件 都可以
Whatever you guys want, it's yours.
我们想要随时征用你的地方开派对
We get to use your place for a party any time we want.
没错 我们可以终身免费吃汉堡
Yeah, and we get free burgers for life.
我可以跟你女朋友亲热亲热
I get to make out with your girlfriend.
想都别想
Forget it!
好吧 那我要这个泡泡椅
Alright, the bean bag chair.
哇 Pete 这真是你吗
Wow! Pete, is that really you?
不是 只是个镜像
No, it's a reflection.
给 把这些花送给Svetlana吧
Here. You can give these to Svetlana.
Eric和Artie随时都可能带着你的新娘回来
Eric and Artie should be back any minute with your bride.
老实说 我 我有点儿紧张
I gotta to be honest, I'm er... I'm a little nervous.
你就要娶一个完全陌生的人为妻
You are about to marry a total stranger.
你有没有认真想过你这是要干什么
Have you really thought about what you're doing?
我很早以前就想过要安定下来了
I've been thinking about settling down for a long long time.
可是你对她什么都不了解啊
But you don't know anything about her.
要是她认为你
What if she thinks you're...
要是她不喜欢你怎么办
What if she doesn't like you?
我会很伤心
I'd be sad
但无论如何我都保证会支持她
but I'd reassure her I'd support her anyway,
因为我做出了这样的承诺
cos I made that commitment.
我将用尽余生呵护她
Then I guess I'd spend the rest of my life being sweet to her.
顺便改变一下她的看法
And also changing her mind.
- 好吧 祝你好运 Pete  - 谢谢
- Well, good luck, Pete. - Thanks.
Svetlana到了 她真是太漂亮了
Svetlana's here, and she is gorgeous!
一定是我看错了目录
I must've misread the catalogue.
看看 她体态多么轻盈啊
Just look how light on her feet she is.
- 嘿 宝贝儿  - 喔喔喔
- Hey, baby. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
呃 各位
Hey, guys.
哦 不好意思 Pete
Oh, hey, Pete...
赶紧把这个东西拿出去
Just get that thing out of here!
- 我会好好处理的  - 放着我来
- I'll take care of it. - I got it.
- 为什么是你来  - 因为是我签收的
- Why you? Cos I signed for it!
你签收的又怎么样 等下
Who cares if you signed for it? Wait a minute.
接我们的来了
That's our ride.
Richie可真是个好人啊 还接你们去上学
How nice of Richie to drive you to school.
那是他为了感谢我出色的工作能力
Yeah, well, that's just his way of saying, "thanks for a job well done."
各位 早上好
Good morning, everybody.
听着 儿子 不要太失望
Now, son, don't be disappointed...
Charlie 说早安
Say good morning, Charlie.
让大家看看你是多么的生机勃勃
Show everyone how alive you are!
我是不是把它照顾得很好啊
Aren't I doing a good job?
是的 是的 很好
Yeah, yeah. Great.
这个小妖精
That little monster!
他一直都在自个买鱼来换
He's been buying his own fish and switchin' 'em!
天知道他买了几个
God only knows how many he's gone through.
- 为此他得付出代价  - 怎么付
- He's gonna pay for this! - How?
我们要是揭穿他 他得知道我们也在作弊了
If we bust him, he'll know we've been cheating, too.
Dewey 我们很自豪
Dewey, your father and I are so proud of
你能把这条鱼照顾得这么好
the way you've taken care of that fish.
是的 你完全证明了你值得我们的信任
Yes, we are. You certainly proved to us you can be trusted.
我们很高兴有你这样
It's so nice to have a boy
认真谨慎 负责任
who's so conscientious, responsible
诚实 永不犯错的儿子
and honest and who always finds a way to do the right thing.
接下来 你有什么话要跟我们说吗
Before we go any further, is there anything you wanna tell me?
我想要个毕尔格猎犬
I want a beagle!
想都别想了 你个小骗子
You're not gonna get it, you little sneak!
我们已经知道了你一直都在换死鱼
We know that you've been switching fish on us,
我昨晚放的那条死鱼今天就被你换成活的了
and that's because I put a dead fish in there last night!
你们作弊 你们都是大骗子
That's cheating! You're cheaters!
虽然是用的土办法教育他
It's not exactly textbook
但是至少我们不用养狗了
but at least we're not getting a dog.
我清理好了我的桌子
I cleaned out my cubby.
你真的不能留下来吗
You're sure I can't talk you into staying?
我妈妈说我需要个健康点的环境
Mom says I need a healthier environment.
她觉得你为了你自己的野心
She thinks it's creepy the way you're using me
利用我有点变态
for your own self-grandiosement.
你根本不需要健康一点的环境
A healthier environment? That's not what you need.
你不可能跟其他普通人进行正常交流
Son, you'll never connect normally with another human being.
他们会觉得你过于天才而嫉妒排挤你
People will recognise your brilliance and loathe you for it.
你能得到的最好结果就是无以名状的恐惧
The best you can hope for is uncomprehending fear
而我能将这种恐惧转换成很好的东西
which I can channel into great things.
- 求求你  - 我可以走了吗
- Please? - Can I go now?
当然 走吧
Sure. Go.
你 我前妻
You, my ex-wife,
我的那些心理治疗师 你们都一样
all of my therapists, you're all the same.
再见了 各位
Bye, guys.
再见 Barton
Bye, Barton.
祝你在美国宇航局好运
Good luck at NASA.
得到密级许可了后记得给我们写信啊
Send us a letter when you get declassified.
Herkabe老师 我们知道你很难过 所以
Mr Herkabe, we know this is hard for you, so...
照片上本来是他爸爸
It's his dad.
我们把你的脸PS上去了
We photo-shopped your head in.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组